<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Cool Stuff</title>
    <link>https://cool-stuff-now.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Cool Stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 18:27:58 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cool-stuff-now.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ant</title>
      <link>https://cool-stuff-now.com/ant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 21:05:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cool-stuff-now.com/ant/</guid>
      <description>SKILL LEVEL: ⭐⭐⭐ SIZE: 8&amp;quot; / 20 cm tall when made with the indicated yarn.
 Ant pattern   MATERIALS:  Light worsted weight yarn in red, blue, white and brown Size C-2 / 2.75 mm crochet hook Safety eyes (10 mm) White embroidery thread Yarn needle Fiberfill for stuffing Optional: metal wire / pipe cleaner  eye white (make 2, in white yarn) Rnd 1: start 6 sc in a magic ring [6] Don’t pull the magic ring too tightly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badger</title>
      <link>https://cool-stuff-now.com/badger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 21:05:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cool-stuff-now.com/badger/</guid>
      <description>SKILL LEVEL: ⭐⭐ SIZE: 8.5” / 21.5 cm tall when made with the indicated yarn.
 badger pattern   MATERIALS:  Worsted weight yarn in white, light gray and dark gray Size C-2 / 3 mm crochet hook Safety eyes (15 mm) Triangular safety nose (22mm x 16mm) Yarn needle Stitch markers Fiberfill for stuffing  foot (make 2, start in dark gray yarn) We start by making two feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>basic stitches</title>
      <link>https://cool-stuff-now.com/basics/basicstitich/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 21:05:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cool-stuff-now.com/basics/basicstitich/</guid>
      <description>If this is your first time making amigurumi, you might find it useful to have a tutorial at hand. With the stitches explained. We suggest you practice the basic stitches before you start making one of the designs. This will help you to read the patterns and abbreviations more comfortably.
chain (abbreviation: ch) This stitch is the basis for many crochet patterns. If you’re working in rows, your first row will be a series of chain stitches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giraffe</title>
      <link>https://cool-stuff-now.com/girraffe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 21:05:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cool-stuff-now.com/girraffe/</guid>
      <description>SKILL LEVEL: ⭐ SIZE: 16.5” / 42 cm tall when made with the indicated yarn.
 giraffe pattern   MATERIALS:  Worsted weight yarn in yellow, beige, brown, pink (leftover) and black (leftover) Size G-6 / 4 mm crochet hook Safety eyes (12 mm) Yarn needle Pins Fiberfill for stuffing  leg (make 4, start in brown yarn) Rnd 1: start 6 sc in a magic ring [6]
Rnd 2: inc in all 6 st [12]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kangoroo</title>
      <link>https://cool-stuff-now.com/kangoroo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 21:05:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cool-stuff-now.com/kangoroo/</guid>
      <description>SKILL LEVEL: ⭐ SIZE: 10” / 25 cm tall when made with the indicated yarn.
 kanguroo pattern   MATERIALS:  Sport weight yarn in brown (3 balls), beige, black (leftover) Size B-1 / 2.5 mm crochet hook Safety eyes (11 mm for Mama and 6 mm for Baby) Yarn needle Pins Stitch markers Fiberfill for stuffing  head and body (in brown yarn) Rnd 1: start 6 sc in a magic ring [6]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>koala</title>
      <link>https://cool-stuff-now.com/koala/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 21:05:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cool-stuff-now.com/koala/</guid>
      <description>SKILL LEVEL: ⭐⭐ SIZE: 4”/ 10 cm tall when made with the indicated yarn.
 koala pattern   MATERIALS:  Light worsted weight yarn in light gray, dark gray, light green, pink (leftover) Chunky weight fluffy yarn in white (the pattern also includes an option for ears made with regular light worsted weight yarn) B-1 / 2.5 mm crochet hook US-7 / 4.5 mm crochet hook Black embroidery thread Sewing needle Yarn needle Stitch markers Fiberfill for stuffing  head (in light gray yarn) Starting at the top of the head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lion</title>
      <link>https://cool-stuff-now.com/lion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 21:05:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cool-stuff-now.com/lion/</guid>
      <description>SKILL LEVEL: ⭐⭐⭐ SIZE: 6” / 15 cm tall when made with the indicated yarn.
 lion pattern   MATERIALS:  Light worsted weight yarn in yellow, brown, pink, orange and black (leftover) B-1 / 2.5 mm crochet hook Safety eyes (9 mm) Yarn needle Pins Stitch markers Fiberfill for stuffing Optional: wire or pipe cleaner  hind leg (make 2, start in brown yarn) Rnd 1: start 7 sc in a magic ring [7]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
